<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="poet_name">Berdaq Ǵarǵabay ulı</string>
    <string name="about_the_poet">About the poet</string>
    <string name="list_of_songs">List of songs</string>
    <string name="about_as">About As</string>
    <string name="settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="berdaq_shayir_qosiqlar_toplami">Musical composition by \nthe poet Berdakh</string>
    <string name="text_baslaw">Lets go …</string>
    <string name="change_language">Change Language</string>
    <string name="text_about_as">About as</string>
    <string name="about_as_text">This application was created by Kalbayeva Aruxan Jengisbayevna, a student of the 433rd group of the faculty of pediatrics and folk medicine of the Tashkent Pediatric Medical Institute.</string>
    <string name="text_about_1">An event dedicated to the life of Berdak was held at the Tashkent Pediatric Medical Institute</string>
    <string name="tv_about_2">On February 14, on the occasion of the 541st anniversary of the birth of writer, scientist, general and statesman Zakhiriddin Muhammad Babur, a lecture was held at the foot of the statue of the poet in Adiblar Avenue on the topic "The role and importance of the legacy of Zakhiriddin Muhammad Babur in educating young people in the spirit of patriotism." a spiritual and educational event took place. In this context, together with Berdaq\'s scholarship holder Utebaeva Bakhargul, we conducted a wide-scale promotion of the Karakalpak poet Berdaq to the students and teachers of the Tashkent Academy of Internal Affairs.</string>
    <string name="tv_about_3">In order to participate in the competition of propaganda and scientific creative works on the theme of Berdaq\'s creativity-interpretation of social life, I gathered students studying at the State Academy of Choreography of Uzbekistan and my comrades according to the poems of our grandfather Berdaq called "The Bride" I went to the mountain with him and organized a meeting. And I prepared this video for participation in the competition.</string>
</resources>
